<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCD</title>
    <link>http://cncd.drone.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CNCD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 22:57:35 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cncd.drone.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Representation Specification (Draft)</title>
      <link>http://cncd.drone.io/spec/ir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 22:57:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cncd.drone.io/spec/ir/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This specification introduces an intermediate representation (IR) for defining continuous delivery pipelines and their container execution environments. A continuous delivery pipeline is an automated manifestation of your process for getting software from version control to release.
Introduction This section is non-normative.
This specification introduces an intermediate representation (IR) for defining continuous delivery pipelines and their container execution environments. The intermediate representation should be machine writable, machine executable, and platform agnostic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline Yaml Specification (Draft)</title>
      <link>http://cncd.drone.io/spec/yaml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 22:57:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cncd.drone.io/spec/yaml/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This specification introduces a YAML format for defining continuous delivery pipelines and their container execution environments. A continuous delivery pipeline is an automated manifestation of your process for getting software from version control to release.
Introduction This section is non-normative.
This specification introduces a YAML format for defining continuous delivery pipelines and their container execution environments. The YAML format described in this specification is a superset of the docker-compose file.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>